Spence, Bill and Andy; Papers apap400
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Old Songs Activities, 1977-2022; 5; 8.78 cubic ft.
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Old Songs Inc. 1999 Fiscal Year Annual Report (March 1, 1999-Febraruy 29, 2000), ca. 2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Andy's 2003 Old Songs Festival Notebook, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Old Songs Festival Pencil, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Old Songs Festival Pin, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Old Songs Inc. 2000 Fiscal Year Annual Report (March 1, 2000-February 28, 2001), ca. 2001 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Andy's 2002 Old Songs Festival Notebook, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 2002 Festival Information, Andy (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March 1, 2001-March 28, 2002), ca. 2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 2002 Old Songs Festival Co., 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival by Anne Glassbourg, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Old Songs Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - "2002 Old Songs Festival", 2003 (Cd 15)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March 1, 2002-March 28, 2003), ca. 2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Guilderland Library Project, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Altamont Fair, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Old Songs Festival Grounds Crew Book, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Photographs Old Songs Building Repair, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March 1, 2003-March 29, 2004), ca. 2004 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Andy's 2004 Old Songs Festival Notebook, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 25th Anniversary Old Songs Festival Calendar, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Andy's 2005 Old Songs Festival Notebook, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Performers, 2005 May (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Arts Day in Albany, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Photograph, Miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March 1, 2004-March 28, 2005), ca. 2005 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Andy's 2008 Old Songs Festival Notebook (1 of 2), 2005-2009 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Andy's 2008 Old Songs Festival Notebook (2 of 2), 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Andy's 2006 Old Songs Festival Notebook (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Calendar, Holiday Greetings from Old Songs, Inc., 2006 (Oversize 3, Folder 9)
  - Songbrick Donors, 2006 (Oversize 3, Folder 10)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Sampler Concert, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival Crew, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 2005/2006 Concert Series (March 1, 2005-March 28, 2006), ca. 2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Andy's 2007 Old Songs Festival Notebook, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Mid Atlantic Arts Foundation Outreach Project, 2006-2007; 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1981 and 1983", 2007 (Cd 16)
  - Photograph, Old Song Event, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Andy, 2007; 2011-2012; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Old Songs Festival Attendance Summary, 2007-2015 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1984 and 1985", 2008 (Cd 17)
  - Old Songs Festival Tickets, 2008 (Oversize 3, Folder 11)
  - Patrick Ball Poster, 2008 (Oversize 3, Folder 12)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March 1, 2007-February 29, 2008), ca. 2008 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Andy's 2009 Old Songs Festival Notebook (1 of 2), 2008-2010 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Andy's 2009 Old Songs Festival Notebook (2 of 2), 2008-2010 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Nanne and Ankie, Quadricentennial on the Hudson, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1986 and 1987", 2009 (Cd 18)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March 1, 2008-February 28, 2009), ca. 2009 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Program Books Ads, 2009-2010 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Andy's 2010 Old Songs Festival Notebook (1 of 2), 2009-2011 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Andy's 2010 Old Songs Festival Notebook (2 of 2), 2009-2011 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Tri-City Trad, 2009-2011 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - "Live Recordings from the 2009 Old Songs Festival", 2010 (Cd 19)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1998 and 1999", 2010 (Cd 20)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Performance, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Old Songs Inc Annual Report (March 1, 2009-February 28, 2010), ca. 2010 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 2011 Old Songs Festival, 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Altamont Fair Contracts, 2010-2013 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1991", 2011 (Cd 21)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1992", 2011 (Cd 22)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1993", 2011 (Cd 23)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1994", 2011 (Cd 24)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1995", 2011 (Cd 25)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1996", 2011 (Cd 26)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Old Songs/Folk Clippings, 2011-2013 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Old Songs Inc. Activities, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1997 Part 2", 2012 (Cd 27)
  - "Old Songs Festival 1998 Part 2", 2012 (Cd 28)
  - Old Songs Festival Poster, 2012 (Oversize 3, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March 1, 2011-February 29, 2012), ca. 2012 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March 1, 2012-February 28, 2013), ca. 2013 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report and Transaction Detail by Account, 2013-2014; 2014 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Class Attendance, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March February 2015), ca. 2015 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Old Songs Festival Notepad, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March -February 2016), ca. 2016 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2017 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Old Songs Inc. Annual Report (March-February 2017), ca. 2017 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Festival Photo Exhibit Information, 2017; Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2018 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Benefit, 2018 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2019 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2020 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2022 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1981 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 14)
  - 1983 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 15)
  - 1984 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 16)
  - 1985 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 17)
  - 1986 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 18)
  - 1987 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 19)
  - 1988 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 20)
  - 1989 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 21)
  - 1990 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 22)
  - 1991 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 23)
  - 1992 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 24)
  - 1993 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 25)
  - 1994 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 26)
  - 1995 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 27)
  - 1996 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 28)
  - 1997 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 1)
  - 1998 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 2)
  - 1999 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 3)
  - 2000 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 4)
  - 2002/1997 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 5)
  - 2006 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 6)
  - 2016 Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 7)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 1, Undated (Cd 29)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 2, Undated (Cd 30)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 3, Undated (Cd 31)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 4, Undated (Cd 32)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 5, Undated (Cd 33)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 6, Undated (Cd 34)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 7, Undated (Cd 35)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 8, Undated (Cd 36)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 9, Undated (Cd 37)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 10, Undated (Cd 38)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 11, Undated (Cd 39)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 12, Undated (Cd 40)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 13, Undated (Cd 41)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 14, Undated (Cd 42)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 15, Undated (Cd 43)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 16, Undated (Cd 44)
  - 2003 Old Songs Festival Disk 17, Undated (Cd 45)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 1, Undated (Cd 46)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 2, Undated (Cd 47)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 3, Undated (Cd 48)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 4, Undated (Cd 49)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 5, Undated (Cd 50)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 6, Undated (Cd 51)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 7, Undated (Cd 52)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 8, Undated (Cd 53)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 9, Undated (Cd 54)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 10, Undated (Cd 55)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 11, Undated (Cd 56)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 12, Undated (Cd 57)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 13, Undated (Cd 58)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 14, Undated (Cd 59)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 15, Undated (Cd 60)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 16, Undated (Cd 61)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 17, Undated (Cd 62)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 18, Undated (Cd 63)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 19, Undated (Cd 64)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 20, Undated (Cd 65)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 21, Undated (Cd 66)
  - 2004 Old Songs Festival Disk 22, Undated (Cd 67)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 1, Undated (Cd 68)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 2, Undated (Cd 69)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 3, Undated (Cd 70)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 4, Undated (Cd 71)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 5, Undated (Cd 72)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 6, Undated (Cd 73)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 7, Undated (Cd 74)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 8, Undated (Cd 75)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 9, Undated (Cd 76)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 10, Undated (Cd 77)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 11, Undated (Cd 78)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 12, Undated (Cd 79)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 14, Undated (Cd 80)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 15A, Undated (Cd 81)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 16A, Undated (Cd 82)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 17, Undated (Cd 83)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 17A, Undated (Cd 84)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 18, Undated (Cd 85)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 19, Undated (Cd 86)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 20, Undated (Cd 87)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 21A, Undated (Cd 88)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Disk 21B, Undated (Cd 89)
  - 2005 Old Songs Festival Photos by Jim Dolen, Undated (Cd 90)
  - Center for Traditional Arts and Agriculture, Dutch Barn Phases, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Center for Traditional Arts and Agriculture Stamps, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Dutch Barn Floor and Structure Plans, Undated (Map-tube 1)
  - Dutch Barn Structure Section #2, Undated (Map-tube 1)
  - Dutch Barns Within 50 Miles of Albany County Open to the Public, Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 8)
  - Live at the Dutch Barn Old Songs Reference Tape, Undated (Cassette 52)
  - Old Songs Festival 0:30 Promo, Undated (Beta 3)
  - Old Songs Festival 0:30 Promo, Undated (Dvcam 1)
  - Old Songs Festival 0:30 Promo, WRGB, 2001 Dates, Undated (Beta 4)
  - Old Songs Festival 102A, Undated (Umatic 3)
  - Old Songs Festival 103A, Undated (Umatic 4)
  - Old Songs Festival, First Track "Sweet Songs from Yesterday Wash Over Me", Undated (Cassette 53)
  - Old Songs Festival, Maxell, Friday Night No. 1, Undated (Cassette 54)
  - Old Songs Festival, Maxell, Friday Night No. 2, Undated (Cassette 55)
  - Old Songs Festival, Maxell, Saturday Night No. 1, Undated (Cassette 56)
  - Old Songs Festival, Maxell, Saturday Night No. 2, Undated (Cassette 57)
  - Old Songs Festival, Maxell, Saturday Night No. 3, Undated (Cassette 58)
  - Old Songs Festival, Maxell, Sunday No. 2, Undated (Cassette 59)
  - Old Songs Festival, Sony, Tape 1, Undated (Cassette 60)
  - Old Songs Festival, Sony, Tape 2, Undated (Cassette 61)
  - Old Songs Festival, Sony, Tape 3, Undated (Cassette 62)
  - Old Songs Festival, Sony, Tape 4, Undated (Cassette 63)
  - Old Songs Festival, Sony, Tape 5, Undated (Cassette 64)
  - Old Songs Festival, Sony, Tape 6, Undated (Cassette 65)
  - Old Songs Festival Stage Building Plans, Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Old Songs Festival, TDK, Undated (Cassette 66)
  - Old Songs Festival, TDK No. 1, Undated (Cassette 67)
  - Old Songs Festival, TDK No. 2, Undated (Cassette 68)
  - Old Songs Festival, TDK No. 3, Undated (Cassette 69)
  - Old Songs Festival, TDK Sunday No. 1, Undated (Cassette 70)
  - Old Songs Materials, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Old Songs Signs, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Photo Exhibit, Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 9)
  - Silver Tube, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Wood Picker, Undated (Artifact-box 1)